

BEN HARPER

Full Stack Web Developer

- (918) 691-1284
- HarperEIS@gmail.com
- LinkedIn
- github.com/HenBarper
- Tulsa, OK

EDUCATION

Diploma of Computer Science and Full Stack Web Development

Atlas School 2023-present

Bachelor of Arts & Sciences University of Oklahoma 2014

SKILLS/TECHNOLOGIES

Web Design

Communication

Organization

Problem Solving

Unity/Godot

C/C#/Python/Java Script

HTML/CSS

LANGUAGE

English

French

ABOUT ME

I am a full stack developer. I joined Atlas School to further develop my technical skills and learn new skills that will make me a more well-rounded developer moving forward in my career. I value teamwork immensely and I'm very excited to enter the workforce and join and learn from a team of experienced developers. I hope to one day be able to lead a team or teams towards a united purpose.

WORK EXPERIENCE

2015-2020

From the End Games LLC. | Tulsa, OK

Lead Programmer/Developer

Lead all elements of design and development for a 2D platformer game called Boogie Bot. This included, game design, coding, architecture, art, animation, finances, marketing, and distribution.

2018-2023

Kreuger Technical | Tulsa, OK

Software Engineer

Work as a developer on projects using c# and the .net framework

 April 2023 - present Atlas School | Tulsa, OK

Student Tutor

Responsible for aiding new students with conceptualizing and executing on coding tasks, giving live-codings to students before beginning larger projects, and attending professional development trainings.

PROJECTS

Boogie Bot

Independent game by From the End Games LLC.

Boogie bot is a 2D platformer game developed for steam using the unity game engine.

Lead Programmer/Devloper

Boogie Bot on Steam

Shell

Unix command interpreter

A group project at Atlas School where we created a simplified version of the Linux Shell.

co-developer

Shell on Github